let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the father of C language?",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Steve Jobs",
      "James Gosling",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a valid C variable name?",
    answer: "int $main;",
    options: [
      "int number;",
      "float rate;",
      "int variable_count;",
      "int $main;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which is valid C expression?",
    answer: "int my_num = 100000;",
    options: [
      "int my_num = 100,000;",
      "int my_num = 100000;",
      "int my num = 1000;",
      "int $my_num = 10000;"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many keywords are there in C language?",
    answer: "32",
    options: [
      "32",
      "33",
      "64",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "C language is a _.",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Procedural oriented programming language",
      "General purpose programming language",
      "Structured programming",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following functions is used to print something in C?",
    answer: "printf()",
    options: [
      "scanf()",
      "printf()",
      "getchar()",
      "putchar()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does the 'continue' statement do in a loop?",
    answer: "Skips the current iteration and continues with the next one",
    options: [
      "Exits the loop",
      "Restarts the loop from the beginning",
      "Skips the current iteration and continues with the next one",
      "Ends the program"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is used to end a statement in C?",
    answer: "Semicolon (;)",
    options: [
      "Colon (:)",
      "Semicolon (;)",
      "Comma (,)",
      "Period (.)"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which header file is essential for using the 'printf()' function?",
    answer: "stdio.h",
    options: [
      "stdlib.h",
      "stdio.h",
      "string.h",
      "math.h"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the size of the 'int' data type in C (on a 32-bit system)?",
    answer: "4 bytes",
    options: [
      "1 bytes",
      "2 bytes",
      "4 bytes",
      "8 bytes"
    ]
  }
];